Isn't this a random move?
No.
How can you call this a random move?
I think
the master is doing this to mess with the opponent's mind.
You've already messed with mine.
I...
Mr. Qin, Mr. Zhao.
I'm sorry, I...
Sorry for what?
Don't you already know
that the simulated flight control failed? So...
So what?
Running back to the archives after a loss,
is this where you belong?
Wu Wei,
what do you mean?
What do you think my archives are?
A backup?
You couldn't get into flight control,
so you come here looking dejected.
If you're going to be like this,
you better leave now.
I won't keep you here.
No.
No, Mr. Zhao, you misunderstood.
That's not what I meant.
I will adjust my attitude right away
and work hard.
When we were young,
we didn't have time for this nonsense.
We spent all our time on work.
Why are you still standing here?
Hurry up and go.
Mr. Zhao, please don't kick me out.
There are ten minutes until the morning meeting.
You'll be late if you don't go now.
Do you mean I can go back to flight control?
Wu Wei.
I think you're usually
quite thick-skinned.
Why do you become a yo-yo when it comes to serious matters?
No, no.
Come back here.
I can tell you now.
Mr. Qian gave me this pen.
I've cherished it all these years.
I'm giving it to you.
Consider yourself lucky, kid.
Mr...
Mr. Qian.
Yes.
It's too precious. No, no, no.
Stop dawdling.
Take it and work hard.
Just don't embarrass the Archives.
Hurry up and go, or I'll regret it.
Yes.
Hurry up.
And,
Wu Wei.
China Aerospace.
I hope you can
live up to this title.
Sorry for making you spend a fortune.
It really hurts.
I did spend a fortune.
But I listened to what you said.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
What is this?
I know you couldn't bear to part with it.
So I bought another one,
an identical pen.
When you weren't looking,
I swapped it.
This is the one Mr. Qian gave you.
Returned intact to its rightful owner.
You're really something.
You old fox.
Alright. Good for you.
The reason Muxing Team failed the flight simulation this time
is that I ignored the actual situation
and insisted on using a radical plan.
Please supervise me.
I will try my best to catch up with everyone
and become a qualified Muxing member.
Mr. Chu.
I know I
lack ability but have a bad temper.
Please be magnanimous
and give me another chance.
Being late in a space mission
could cause an accident.
Sit down quickly.
Yes.
All right, let's start the meeting.
I believe you've heard
that the center
has been preparing for the Xingqiao relay satellite mission
to provide communication support for Haoyue 4's
landing on the far side of the moon.
This is also the world's first
telemetry, tracking, command, and relay communication
at the Earth-Moon Lagrange L2 point.
Currently, we have selected
the halo orbit at the Earth-Moon L2 point
as the Xingqiao orbit.
So what we need to do
is to help Xingqiao find a path
that smoothly leads to the halo orbit.
Later, the four of you will
participate in some of the work,
starting with orbit data calculation.
You can go to the institute in a while
and bring the data back.
Since the simulated flight is over,
from now on,
I will hold you to higher standards.
I hope you can pull yourselves together
and meet the challenge.
The detector workshop.
Take a look.
This is the most important department in satellite manufacturing.
From assembly to integration,
and the many tests required for R&D,
the satellites you see operating in orbit
are all born here.
Look at this.
This is our Haoyue 4 Xingqiao relay satellite.
What do you think?
Don't blink.
This is our Earth-Moon communication
and data relay station.
It can transmit the scientific data
of Haoyue-4, which landed on the lunar far side,
back to Earth in real time.
It's equivalent to
a fiber-optic network relay station between the Earth and the moon.
Precisely because it is blocked by the moon itself,
we must build Xingqiao on the Earth-Moon extension line
to achieve communication visibility with the lunar far side and Earth.
Ultimately,
this is a powerful attempt by humanity
to explore deep space.
It has great scientific
and engineering significance.
My God.
This is simply industrial aesthetics.
With this star bridge,
our journey to the far side of the moon
will be a smooth ride.
This is so spectacular.
I should have studied the next major over,
so I wouldn't have to wrestle with data all day.
For such a huge project,
we definitely have to cooperate.
Right?
This is the result of the joint efforts of hundreds of sister units,
tens of thousands of scientists,
and engineers.
It relies on collective wisdom, strength, and struggle.
Of course,
your Brother Xiu also gets some credit for this.
Testing over there.
I hope I can stay
to help the probe land on the moon.
Mr. You,
the orbit data you need to calculate is over here.
Follow me.
All right.
This way.
This.
Don't just stand there. Take it.
The orbit data to be calculated later
is all here.
Catch.
This is...
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Who put
this here?
Did you receive the cup Wu Wei gave you?
You can use that cup
to make hot tea or something.
Don't always use paper cups for water.
Jiajia,
the registration for this year's Space Orbit Competition
has started.
You guys in Flight Control should participate.
Hello, Director Cao.
I think it will be tough this year.
With such heavy tasks, how would they have time?
Didn't Mr. Qin tell you?
He told me to come to you.
It's up to you.
I know you have heavy tasks,
but haven't a few newcomers arrived this year?
Let the kids participate
and practice.
The simulation flight failed.
Are you still counting on them?
Is it that bad?
They're already quite upset about the simulation flight failure.
I heard the competition is harder this year,
and the opponents are stronger.
I'm worried that if I go,
I might not do well in the competition.
Never mind. Let's talk about it later.
What should we do then?
How about you ask other departments?
Aren't you making things difficult for me?
Director Cao.
I haven't recovered from the flight simulation,
and now I have to calculate new orbital data.
So stressful.
I'm traumatized.
I'm afraid of making mistakes in whatever I do.
This is a place where results speak for themselves.
We messed up before.
Don't blame them for looking down on us.
If we want them to respect us,
we have to conquer them.
How do we conquer them?
Today I heard a Director Cao
talking to Jia about this.
I think it's our chance.
I know this competition.
It's an international event
held every two years.
In recent years, it's been dominated by the World Aerospace Association
and the Western Space Development Alliance.
The opponents are too strong.
Yes.
If we fight,
we should fight the strongest.
Second place was the Chinese team's
best result before.
Today, Director Cao
wanted to ask Sister Jia
to let our department participate in this competition,
but was rejected.
I think
we can sign up ourselves.
Right?
This competition
is the most professional one in deep space exploration
and orbit design.
If we get any ranking,
we will take off.
But Sister Jia refused.
How can we participate?
Just don't let her know.
We can finish it in our spare time.
Then we can redeem ourselves.
Isn't it a win-win?
I guess it's doable.
If we don't get good grades,
it's the participation that counts.
If we give it a try
and get a good result,
we'll hit the jackpot.
If you are all okay with it,
then I have no objections.
Ying Ziqi, join us.
Of course.
I'm counting on Master Ying to dominate the field.
Are you going or not? What do you say?
Is proving yourself that important to you?
Of course it's important.
Our workload is so heavy right now.
We shouldn't distract ourselves with other things.
I already said we'd participate in our spare time.
Besides, don't you want to do more?
Is that necessary?
Forget it. Suit yourself.
I have a way.
But for this competition,
we need at least six people.
It's fine.
I know a bigger master
who isn't as arrogant as him.
Later,
I'll introduce two friends to you.
Come on, cheers!
Nan,
why aren't you having fun?
I'm not in the mood.
Our Muxing Team is short-handed right now.
Wei,
are we really not bringing Qi?
He didn't want to come himself.
I can't force him, right?
I'm telling you,
from my observation,
he responds to persuasion but not coercion.
Dealing with someone like Ying Ziqi
requires some tricks.
Actually, I already have a little plan.
It has three steps.
Is it treating, beheading,
and making them your dog?
Those are the old three steps.
I have the new three steps.
Dafu, Chashao.
Coming!
Let's take a picture.
Let me post it on Moments first. All right.
Step two.
The oriole behind.
Wei,
that's not how you use that idiom.
What did you get on your Chinese exam
to question me?
But if we isolate him like this,
isn't it bullying?
No.
We are bullying him
so he will join us.
Execute step three.
So mysterious.
Hey you.
Have you thought about it?
Are you still going to join?
Don't you have enough people?
I do,
but out of the kindness of my heart,
I saved a spot for you.
Do you want to participate that much?
Because this competition is worth it.
Since you invited me so sincerely,
I guess I could.
But I have a condition.
A condition?
Of course.
I'm there to compete,
not to argue with you.
To avoid unnecessary disagreements,
I have to set a rule.
During the competition, you have to listen to me,
especially regarding key decisions.
If we all listen to you,
what's the point of a team?
I will consider the team's opinions.
But if you don't trust my judgment,
why did you ask me?
We trust your judgment, of course.
So if Wu Wei listens to you entirely,
you'll join us, right?
You make all the important decisions,
and we'll cooperate professionally.
I think that's fine.
That's great.
See?
However,
when I say listen to me,
I also mean in daily life.
During the competition,
all dorm chores
are your responsibility.
Chores too?
You're such a little cutie.
What?
It's all for the competition.
In a messy dorm environment,
I can't work in peace.
I think that's reasonable.
I think it's reasonable too.
I don't think it is.
He's taking the opportunity to blackmail me.
If I agree,
it would be a total humiliation.
Not really.
Yes, it is.
Anyway, that's my condition.
Think about it.
Wei,
I feel like he's not falling into the trap.
We failed, didn't we?
Luring him into the trap
involves two small steps.
Lure him,
into the trap.
A willing victim lets himself be caught.
That's the only way to deal with his kind.
Let's discuss tonight
the next step.
The trap.
Bro, give it a kick.
Let's go.
The Earth is the cradle of humanity,
but mankind cannot stay in the cradle forever.
If people are no longer satisfied
with being citizens of the solar system,
how should they migrate to the Milky Way?
The topic of this competition is
the design of migration orbits in the Milky Way.
Galactic migration.
With the immigrable Milky Way as the background,
over a period of 90 million years,
three types of interstellar spaceships will be used
to spread humans throughout the Milky Way.
Taking 100,000 stars in the Milky Way
as immigrable targets,
they are distributed
within a range of about 210,000 light-years in diameter.
The migration pod uses speed maneuvers
to reach the star.
The star is then immediately colonized.
Each fast ship
can only rendezvous with one star.
The rendezvoused star
is immediately colonized.
That means
we have to compare migration plans.
What a sci-fi topic!
Yeah.
This is the first time
a sci-fi mission is used as the background.
Hello?
Xiaobai.
Long time no see.
What?
Space Trajectory Design Competition?
It's actually doable.
I'll check the problems later.
Go on. Go on. Go on.
I'll give you some ideas.
Wei, Brother Wei.
There's another rule below.
This competition uses
a real-time scoring and online ranking system.
One week after the problems are released,
the submission window opens.
It lasts for 15 days
before the submission window closes.
The time bonus multiplier
depends on the submission time of the proposal.
This problem is way too hard.
Hard is good.
It means it's highly valuable.
It's fine. Don't worry.
We...
Let's take our time and figure it out.
No, Wei.
I really think it's a bit hard.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'll copy down their formulas first.
In a two-body model,
gravity is inversely proportional to the square of the radius.
But the problem given is that
at the very center of the Milky Way,
gravity and radius
have an inverse relationship of a higher-degree polynomial.
So,
when calculating an interstellar transfer orbit,
you can't simply apply
the common formulas under a two-body gravity environment
and methods.
It's actually not hard.
It mainly lies in the design of the migration tree.
Right.
That's exactly what I mean.
Not hard, right?
I'll hang up now.
I'm a bit hungry.
I'll grab a bite and call you back.
The questions this year weren't that hard.
Good luck to you all.
Keep bragging.
Qi, Qi, Qi.
Come, come, come.
Sit down.
Qi,
don't be mad.
I really need to criticize you today.
You see,
you have strong working skills
and a rigorous attitude,
but there is a very serious problem.
You don't take care of yourself at all.
It's so stuffy staying in your room every day.
What if you get sick from it?
You should come out and chat with us more.
Right?
Getting some fresh air is good for you, isn't it?
Here,
I'll pour you some coffee.
No need.
I'm a little hungry.
Hungry?
Qu Ruonan,
are you hungry?
Yes, you're hungry, right?
Then we need to get some high-quality protein.
Just in time. Wu Wei,
didn't you say
you prepared some food?
I'm a bit hungry too.
Yeah, Wei.
I could smell
the ribs.
How about we sit down and chat
while eating?
Right, Wu Wei.
You go make it first.
Qi, what were you saying?
Share it with us.
What immigrant tree?
Don't let him fool you.
Look at him. What does he know?
It's actually very simple. There are just three points.
To use an analogy,
it's like a lush tree providing shade everywhere,
while saving water and fertilizer.
If you want to show off your IQ, just say it.
Stop being so mysterious.
Got it?
The score for the migration scheme competition
is determined by three parts:
the time reward coefficient,
the number and uniformity of the destination planets,
and the fuel coefficient.
Actually, the process of migrating to the galaxy
is about launching ships from the solar system,
planting seeds in the galaxy,
and letting them take root and sprout.
The roots grow into trunks,
the trunks grow into branches,
the branches grow leaves,
eventually becoming a towering tree.
If you want a high score,
you must make the tree grow lush,
working together to provide shade everywhere.
Of course,
you must also consider saving water and fertilizer as much as possible.
So our submission plan requires
a large quantity,
even distribution,
and low fuel consumption, right?
That's the idea.
You're amazing, Ying!
Come join us!
With Ying here,
I think we have a chance.
Yeah.
We are all in the same boat,
competing together.
Why would you go out of your way to help outsiders?
Right?
And then?
Is someone coming today?
That's a lot of food.
Are you cooking?
You're cooking.
I'll cook.
It's all prepared for you.
So he's cooking. Is that appropriate?
Appropriate. Of course it is.
Please.
Here it is.
Qi, please go ahead.
You're too slow.
Please go ahead.
So slow.
We were starving to death before you served the food.
Even food can't shut your mouth.
Go do your own things after eating.
Are you setting me up?
You're eating my cooking,
and you think I'm tricking you?
So do you agree to my conditions?
Forget about conditions.
We Muxing Team are a family.
Don't do that oppression and exploitation stuff.
Why are you looking at me?
He's manipulating me.
Look at him.
There is no manipulation here.
We are all brothers.
Qi did us the honor of eating Wei's ribs.
That means he agreed to join us.
Appreciate the honor.
When did you two sell me out?
We are united.
Do you know what unity is?
We are determined to defeat
the foreign Space Development Alliance team.
This is what you said yourself, Wu Wei.
Alright, agreed.
I have one more condition.
Let me tell you.
You shouldn't push your luck.
You shouldn't be insatiable.
At least you shouldn't.
Bring Xiaoba to the dorm.
Xiaoba?
My turtle, Xiaoba.
Can I bring it to the dorm?
As its former owner,
it's not too much to ask to see it every day, right?
Not at all.
Really not.
Okay, fine.
Deal.
Words are not enough.
You have to sign an agreement.
I have to sign an agreement with you?
In case you can't do it,
there should be some punishment.
No problem.
Piece of cake.
Forget about the punishment,
but I can set up
a points system for us.
Is that okay?
Okay.
To be fair,
when Wei's chore points
reach a certain level,
Qi has to help out too.
That's not too much to ask, right?
Okay.
When our Muxing Team goes down in aerospace history,
this agreement
will be the token witnessing
our glorious beginning.
Wait.
This pen won't do.
Once you sign with this pen,
there's no going back.
Is there a difference?
Do you know the origin of this pen?
It has a long history.
Mr. Qian gave it to Mr. Zhao,
and Mr. Zhao gave it to me.
Do you know what this is?
The inheritance of history,
the continuation of spirit.
A globally limited edition,
co-branded by Qian.
Let me see.
Take it easy.
Mr. Zhao is too generous.
Look at who he's giving it to.
Can we start?
Pour me a cup of coffee.
Do you guys want some?
Us?
Do you want some?
They want some.
Three cups.
Don't forget to bring Xiaoba tomorrow.
Okay, okay.
Your brother Xiaoba.
Come on.
Time to eat. Let's eat.
Time to eat. Time to eat.
Come on.
Let's serve the rice first.
You are getting better at this.
Let's check the progress
of the data calculation.
You just joined Flight Control.
Keeping up with the pace is a basic requirement.
That's all.
Don't you think
you should have finished it earlier with your ability?
I thought I didn't need to finish it.
You have the best qualifications,
so you must hold yourself to high standards.
You can't let Mr. Qin down.
You can't slack off, dawdle, or rest on your laurels.
Yours.
The task just started,
so it might be a little slow.
That's acceptable.
Keep up the pace.
You shouldn't be this inefficient.
I was worried about making mistakes,
so I checked it a few more times.
Even if you checked it a few more times,
you shouldn't be this slow.
Look at the others,
they are much faster than you.
You have a solid foundation in algorithms.
You need to be bolder.
How can you finish the task at this pace?
Are you going to make everyone wait for you?
I understand. I'll speed up.
You too.
Speed it up.
Well, I think
you young people.
How about this.
After the data is uploaded to the system,
you can get off work.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Go ahead.
Jiajia,
have you heard anything about the professional title evaluation
that was submitted a long time ago?
Any news?
I almost forgot if you hadn't mentioned it.
I remember it was submitted
before the first rendezvous mission.
I've been too busy lately to ask.
How about this?
I'll ask Mr. Qin later.
It's not that urgent.
It's mainly because my girlfriend has been rushing me lately.
Girlfriend?
Good things are coming.
Pretty much.
She's coming to Beijing
and looking for a receiving unit.
After coming to Beijing and getting married,
we can't still live in the dormitory, right?
So she gave me an ultimatum.
I have to get the title this year.
I need to get a bigger place.
Don't worry.
You've submitted so many papers.
As for me,
I've been dragging my feet on this one.
Don't be so anxious, you two.
Especially you, Mr. Li.
Really, Mr. Li, just ask Jiajia.
When I first married my husband right after graduation,
we had absolutely nothing.
Our pockets were completely empty.
Life just goes on, step by step.
Really.
If my girlfriend were as calm as you,
I wouldn't be worried.
Her family is well-off.
You know, she can't marry me
and live worse than she did at home.
Look at Brother Hou, didn't he eventually...
It's fine.
Don't overthink it.
I'll ask for you later.
I'll let you know when I do.
You'll definitely be fine.
Okay, thank you then.
I'll be leaving first.
Okay.
Remember to treat Jiajia and me to a meal later.
Sure, no problem.
I'm off. Bye.
Bye.
Mom, when are you coming back?
You promised to tell me a story.
It's been half a month.
Did Chang'e finally meet Hou Yi?
Didn't Dad already tell you this?
Dad's stories are boring.
Dad's cooking is awful too.
I can't even eat it.
Mr. Li,
you've dedicated yourself to the country and your career.
The burden of the family
has fallen solely on me.
Alright, you get back to work.
I'll put the child to sleep.
Say goodnight to Mom.
Mom.
Don't work overtime anymore. Come back soon.
OK.
Say bye-bye to Mom.
Bye-bye.
Go to sleep.
The calculation volume is so large right now,
and time is tight for the competition.
I'm really worried I can't do well in both,
and won't be able to stay.
You have your own advantages.
You can be more confident.
The lights in Beijing are so bright.
So bright that I can only see
the brightest stars in the sky.
You know what?
In my hometown,
as soon as the sun goes down,
everyone basically goes to rest.
With no lights,
all the stars in the sky can be seen.
When I was young,
to get into my dream school
and to come to Beijing,
I worked desperately hard on practice questions
and memorizing texts.
When everyone else was resting,
only the stars accompanied me.
I chose to come to Flight Control at first
to play it safe.
I wanted to stay in this city that's brighter than the stars.
But I didn't expect
that after coming here, I'd find
this place is full of hidden talents.
The sense of inferiority I had when I first entered college
came back.
Actually, I quite envy you.
You are not only capable and strong,
but your ideas for proposals are also very clear.
Unlike me,
I couldn't help with the flight simulation task.
And now, with the relay satellite data,
I'm working slower than all of you.
Don't be discouraged.
Work is different from school after all.
Oh, and there's Wu Wei.
Actually, after interacting with him these days,
I found he's quite unique.
He has this
reckless courage.
I just feel
he can succeed at whatever he does.
If he has a dream, he'll pursue it.
I believe
even if the simulation failed this time,
and he took a hit,
he'll get right back up and keep going.
Ying Ziqi, you know what?
You two are actually quite similar.
Him and me?
Similar?
Even though I'm a STEM girl,
I'm actually a very good judge of character.
You both have a kind of confidence.
Yours comes from your competence,
and Wu Wei's comes from his persistence.
I have neither of these.
I came to Beijing,
and I can only rely on myself.
Here,
I face even greater challenges.
You are right.
This is a place where you stay based on competence.
If I want to stay,
I have to rely on my own competence
and move forward step by step.
Actually, I really envy you guys.
Envy us?
I envy that you have dreams
and can fight for them.
I even envy you for having pressure
that can motivate you.
As for me,
I'm like a satellite that hasn't entered orbit.
We strive for a stable job
and a residency status.
For such simple,
even somewhat
vulgar dreams,
you actually envy us?
How can dreams be ranked?
This is my
first time hearing someone say that.
A very annoying person once said,
passion itself
is the meaning of passion.
Who?
Eat. It relieves stress.
Thank you.
The plan for the track competition is so hard.
Jia's assignment isn't done either. What should we do?
The track data in our plan is the difficult part.
I think Jia has done a similar plan before.
That's great.
Wei.
Jia is your boss.
Go ask her for it so we can use it as a reference.
I think it could work.
But how do I bring it up?
I entered the competition behind her back to begin with.
You know how it is.
Wei.
I'll teach you a trick.
Just flatter her like crazy.
Flatter her hard, nonstop.
Trust me, in less than three days,
no one can resist that.
Really?
Come on.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
If we can get the data,
it'll save us a lot of time.
You know
how tight our schedule is right now.
Yeah, I know, but
how do I flatter her?
I, Cai, will teach you.
Workplace flattery has three main steps.
Step one,
start with her work ability.
Ask for advice humbly to make her look good.
Step two, start with the details.
Show concern for her well-being.
Step three is the most important.
Be persistent and relentless.
Give me an example.
Give us an example.
Qi loves chocolate, right?
Do you know how to flatter?
Ying Ziqi.
You are like my chocolate,
sweet, cute,
and beautiful.
Alright, alright.
Chinese ship.
Why do people flatter?
I skipped breakfast and feel a bit hungry.
Does anyone have food?
I have some bread in my drawer.
I'll give it to you later.
I didn't sleep well last night.
I'm a little sleepy now.
I'll go get some water.
Wu Wei.
Jia, Yan,
Li, Xiu, morning.
Why are you suddenly so enthusiastic?
He's finally figured it out
and learned to respect his seniors.
A good day starts in the morning.
Why are you suddenly so hardworking?
The floor is so dirty, but you don't sweep it.
Why are you cleaning the ceiling?
Because my seniors
are my ceiling.
That's a good one.
Keep it up.
Don't forget it once your enthusiasm wears off.
Then later,
while you're at it,
take out the trash, will you?
No problem.
Oh my god, Jia.
Jia.
Look at the way you walk.
People would think you're a runway model.
Jia,
you are indeed the beauty of our flight control center.
With your figure, it's a waste not to be a model.
How does the saying go?
You're a runaway princess.
Did you take the wrong medicine?
Jia,
you are so dazzling, so brilliant,
and radiant.
You warm and shine upon us like the sun.
Don't you like hearing that, Jia?
Are you drunk?
Or still half asleep?
Or just have too much free time?
No, I just can't help myself around you, Jia.
It's uncontrollable. My heart is fluttering.
Okay, enough.
If you're sick, see a doctor. If you're unwell, take a leave.
I'm just full of admiration for you, Jia,
and want to learn from you.
All right.
Finish cleaning and get back to work quickly.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Didn't you want to learn and improve?
That's perfect.
Before you get to work,
the ceiling on
this entire floor isn't very clean.
It needs to be cleaned.
We aerospace professionals
must be well-rounded in all aspects.
The entire floor?
What, you don't want to?
Okay.
Then get to work.
The entire floor.
You just want to tire the poor guy out.
How did it go, Wei?
What do you mean?
She didn't buy it at all,
and even said I was crazy.
Is it your problem
or mine?
How could it be my problem?
Besides, why would I set you up?
I suggest you guys just give up.
Don't underestimate Jia.
Your trick definitely won't work on her.
My trick is absolutely foolproof.
Do you know what
the key to my trick is?
Be thick-skinned
and persistent.
Persistent.
The names of the spacecrafts and their related missions in this drama are fictional.
Ying Deqian, He Qiang
Chen Bing
Zhao Qiangjun
Wu Jianguo
Xiaobai
Wang Yiqi, Feng Shuaige, Tang Zixuan, Fu Jingyun, Wang Zhenglin, Qin Dehang, Zhang Haoming, Wang Zihan
Production Team
Line Producer Zhao Xuguang
Lighting Team
Lighting Technician
Sound Recordist
Painter
Producer
Makeup and Hair Team
Data Management Li Peiyuan, Tong Zhenzhong
Legal Team
Equipment Support
Beijing Liushun Huihuang Film and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Chuangxiang Xinshijie Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Negative Matcher
VFX Production Company
Beijing Ziyouxunhuan Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
VFX Supervisor Zhang Zheng
Beijing Moyingdongli Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Packaging Designer
Compositor
Dubbing Team
Bian Jiang Studio
Music Production Team
Theme Song 'Mu Xing'
Singer
Lyricist
Poster Design Team
Acknowledgments
Tianjin Xingye Property Group Co., Ltd.
Tianjin Jingmao Metal Products Co., Ltd.
Publicity Department of the CPC Tianjin Nankai District Committee
Publicity Department of the CPC Tianjin Jinghai District Committee
Jingwumen Zhonghua Wulin Park
Jizhou Cheshenjia Scenic Area
Guidance Unit
News and Publicity Center of China National Space Administration
Zhengzhou New Force Film Co., Ltd.
Horgos New Force Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.